http://www.gosuburban.com/privacy-policy

HomeTestimonialsE-Newsletter SignupCareersAboutExperienceIndustriesQualityOur BrandsPython Protective Sleeves + CoversProductsWrap SleeveTubular SleeveBundling StrapsIndustriesApplicationsDef Tank CoverCustom & ConfiguredContact UsPython SearchTsunami Compressed Air SolutionsProductsAir FiltrationAir DryersBreathing AirDrainsUltra Flo Spray HoseParts & AccessoriesApplicationsContact UsTsunami SearchLubeMinder Oil + Grease SystemsProductsOiling SystemsGrease SystemsParts & AccessoriesOur PartnersContact UsLubeminder SearchResourcesCatalogs & ManualsInstructional VideosRequest a WebinarFAQsContact UsIndustriesConstructionAgricultureTransportationIndustrialUtilitiesDefenseSitemapNews & PressPython's All New Full-Spectrum Application ProtectionTsunami's Pure 5T is Making WavesHow a Tsunami Regenerative Dryer can save your Dust Collector SystemEvents
Privacy Policy
HomePrivacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY Suburban Manufacturing, Inc. respects your privacy and our site visitors' information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future. Information Collected If you request or submit information to us by sending an Email via info@gosuburban.com or by filling out a "contact" form, we may save your Email address as well as any other information you provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, Email, or phone to convey information about our solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your Email and other information will not be sold to any third party. Information Collected by Others This notice addresses only Suburban Manufacturing, Inc.'s website policy, and does not apply to sites that users access via links from our site. Suburban Manufacturing, Inc. is not responsible for the information collecting policies of other sites, for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, or for the information or content contained therein. Often, links to other websites are provided solely on the basis that they may contain useful information for our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites. Cookies Suburban Manufacturing, Inc.'s website does not use cookies. Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information If you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an Email with "Remove personal information" in the subject line. Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information Suburban Manufacturing, Inc. may disclose information when legally compelled to do so: when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so or for the protection of our legal rights. Periodic Policy Changes Please note that Suburban Manufacturing, Inc. reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page. This policy statement is made in the name of Suburban Manufacturing, Inc. and is effective as of August 13, 2014. This statement does not create an agreement between Suburban Manufacturing, Inc. and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party. Contact Us: Suburban Manufacturing, Inc. 10531 Dalton Ave NE Monticello, MN 55362 Toll-Free: 800.782.5752 Phone: 763.295.5635 Fax: 763.295.6601 Email: info@gosuburban.com Website: www.gosuburban.com
